saltlending.com 2019-12-04

# Read the SALT Lending Privacy Policy

Last Revised: January 29, 2019

Salt Lending Holdings, Inc., (SALT), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our platform accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with SALT of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.

THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy shall apply to SALT and any subsidiary company of SALT listed below or that may be later organized, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.SaltLending.com and any subsidiary website listed below or that may be later organized you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this privacy policy.

Subsidiary Company: Salt Platform, LLC

Subsidiary Website: www.saltlending.com

Collection of Information: SALT’S website(s) collects various types of information, such as:

Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested. Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs. Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, and completed membership forms. Additionally, telephone conversations and electronic communications such as e-mails and instant messaging, between you and SALT and our subsidiaries in connection with your use of our website may be recorded. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site. We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service. It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.

Use of Information Collected: SALT may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.SaltLending.com and our subsidiaries. SALT and our subsidiaries may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered. SALT does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties. SALT may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public. SALT may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon SALT and/or our website; Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of SALT; and Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.SaltLending.com. and/or the general public. Children Under Age of 13: SALT does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.

FullStory: SALT utilizes FullStory, a third-party SaaS analytics service (FullStory), to help enhance your experience when using the SALT website and platform. FullStory allows SALT to watch a video playback of user sessions on our platform, enabling meaningful insight into your experience, as an effective way to identify usability problems and other areas for improvement. Information about FullStory can be found at www.fullstory.com. FullStory ensures that your data is securely stored and accessible only to SALT, however SALT has configured the use of FullStory to exclude any personal identifiable information.

However, if despite the benefits and improvements that FullStory helps SALT to implement, you wish to prevent SALT from using FullStory to record activity, you can opt-out of FullStory at https://www.fullstory.com/optout. Opting out will create a cookie that tells FullStory to turn off recording. The presence of this cookie is required to continue opting out, which means if you clear your browser cookies, you will have to opt-out again.

Unsubscribe or Opt-Out: All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to info@saltlending.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

Links To Other Web Sites: Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. SALT does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.

Security: SALT shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control. The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users' trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information. In addition, SALT is a licensee of TRUSTe. The website is also secured by VeriSign.

Changes to Privacy Policy: SALT reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of this Privacy Policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at www.saltlending.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time SALT decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.

Acceptance of Terms: Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within this Privacy Policy. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

How to Contact Us: If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.

Email: info@saltlending.com

Telephone Number: (303) 243-5018
